[
{
"ques_no": "1",
"question": "C# is developed by ?",
"a": "Apple",
"b": "Google",
"c": "Microsoft",
"d": "IBM",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "2",
"question": "File extension of C# file ?",
"a": ".cs",
"b": ".c",
"c": ".cpp",
"d": ".java",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "a"
},
{
"ques_no": "3",
"question": "main methods in C# is ?",
"a": "start()",
"b": "Main()",
"c": "run()",
"d": "begin()",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "4",
"question": "C# is",
"a": "UI",
"b": "Image",
"c": "Music",
"d": "High-level language",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "5",
"question": "C# code runs on ?",
"a": "JVM",
"b": "CLR",
"c": "CPU only",
"d": "None",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "6",
"question": "How to print in C# ?",
"a": "echo()",
"b": "print()",
"c": "printf()",
"d": "Consol.WriteLine()",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "7",
"question": "C# is used for ?",
"a": "Games",
"b": "Web Apps",
"c": "Desktop apps",
"d": "All",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "8",
"question": "Char Stores ?",
"a": "Word",
"b": "Sentance",
"c": "One letter",
"d": "Number",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "9",
"question": "String stores ?",
"a": "True/False",
"b": "Numbers",
"c": "Letters",
"d": "Text",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "10",
"question": "if is used for ?",
"a": "Loops",
"b": "Printing",
"c": "Conditions",
"d": "Classes",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
}
]